日常工作
翻译：墨冰  压制：感康小快客
校对 & 后期：@Phuckq
误拨电话
【三次元成瘾者康复中心】倾情奉献
更多动画 新浪@Kresent
本字幕仅供学习交流 严禁用于商业用途
天哪 昨晚真是绝赞 绝赞
Man, last night was the best. The best.
是啊 挺好玩的
Yeah, it was pretty fun.
你看 玛格丽特和艾琳在"游戏之夜"来我们这玩
I mean, Margaret and Eileen over for "Game Night,"
一切进展顺利
and nothing went wrong.
没有时空穿越 没有电玩怪物 没人受伤
No space portals, no video demons, nobody got hurt.
除了艾琳和我打了你的屁屁
Except for Eileen and I whipping your butts.
无所谓 我玩得挺开心
Whatever, I had fun.
哥们 拜托 来帮把手啊
Dude, come on, help out.
如果不把这块收拾好的话
Benson's not going to let us have people over anymore
本森再也不会让我们带人来玩了
if we leave this place a mess.
还有 以防你玩坏我的新手机 把它放下
And put down my new phone before you break it.
好嘞 马上
Ok, just a sec.
我给你做个新的壁纸
I'm making you a new custom wallpaper.
厕所队长
衰人
我要把这些运到垃圾场去
All right, I'm going to take this stuff to the dump.
你要把这些垃圾运到你脸上才对吧
You mean you're going take that trash to your face.
手机给我
Gimme my phone.
昨晚玩得爽 今天心情好 算你走运
You're lucky I'm in a good mood from last night.
♪跟玛格丽特一起玩 感觉真不错♪
♪A-hanging with Margaret just-a feels so good.♪
♪像我早就预知过♪
♪like I knew it would.♪
♪一起欢笑 一起享乐♪
♪Laughing together and-a having a blast.♪
♪希望这一直持续着♪
♪And I hope it lasts forever.♪
♪不敢相信 她是那么火辣♪
♪I can't believe how hot she is.♪
♪让我内心 纠结如麻♪
♪Makes my insides feel like knotted twists.♪
♪她漂亮的脸蛋和长长的腿♪
♪Her pretty face and those long, long legs,♪
♪希望我们有一天 不只是朋友♪
♪and I hope someday we are more than just friends!♪
♪噢 玛格丽特 噢 玛格丽特♪
♪Oh, Margaret. Oh Margaret!♪
♪无论你站或坐在我身边 都让我欣喜♪
♪I love it when you stand or sit right next to me.♪
♪你感觉到了吗♪
♪Can't you see?♪
♪你我的未来比大海还光明~♪
♪Your future with me is brighter than the ocean...♪
啥 "比大海还光明"
What? "Brighter than the ocean?"
如果你已录制完成本条信息 请按1
If you are satisfied with your message, press 1.
删除或重录语音信息 请按2
To delete or re-record your message, press 2.
玛格丽特
不 不 不 删 删 删了
No! No! No! Delete! delete! Delete!
信息已发送 再见
Message sent. Goodbye.
我了个...
Oh, my...
瑞格比
Rigby!
哥们 完蛋了 她再也不会理我了
Dude, its over! She's never gonna talk to me again!
-谁  -玛格丽特
- Who? - Margaret!
我刚在车里唱有关她的歌 结果被录下来发去她语音信箱了
I was singing about her in the cart, and it recorded it to her voicemail!
你一开始就别打她电话呗
Why did you call her in the first place?
我坐在手机上了 意外啊
I sat on my phone. It was an accident!
你拿屁股误拨了电话
You butt dialed her?
她肯定觉得我是个彻底的衰货
She must think I'm a total loser!
拜托 不会那么悲剧的
Come on! It can't be THAT bad!
我唱的是首关于她有多漂亮
I sang a song about how hot she was,
我多想永远跟她在一起的歌
and how I wanted us to be together forever.
好吧 是够悲剧的 不过我们来挽回一下
Okay, that's really bad. But we can fix it!
我只要给她打电话 说那信息发错了就行了
I'll just call her, and say the message was for someone else!
哥们 别啊 那不是帮倒忙吗
Dude, no! That'll make it even worse!
嗨 我是玛格丽特
Hi, this is Margaret...
嘿 玛格丽特
Hey Margaret.
我正在上班 请在哔声后留言
I'm at work right now, so leave a message after the beep.
她还在上班
She's still at work.
也就是说她还没来得及看语音信箱呢
Which means she hasn't checked her voicemail yet!
哥们... 我们必须拿到她的手机然后删掉那条信息
Dude... we have to get to her phone and erase that message.
好嘞 她在那儿呢
Okay, there she is.
啊不要
Oh no!
够狠
Burned!
她一看是你发的信息 都不带打开的
She saw that you left a message, and didn't even CHECK it!
- 太冷酷了 哥们  - 闭嘴
- That's cold, man. - Shut up.
这样 我进去以后开始跟她聊天
Okay, I'll go in and start talking to her.
你从边上溜进去
You go in through the side,
钻到她身后的桌子底下 把手机偷偷拿过来
go underneath the table behind her, and swipe her phone.
赞 小爷这手生来就是为了顺手牵羊的
Love it! These hands were MADE for swiping!
玛格丽特
Margaret!
喔 你好啊摩迪凯 还好吗
Oh, hey Mordecai! How's it going?
呃 你知道的 还好
Oh, you know. Good.
还~好
Good...
嘿 我昨天真的玩得很开心
Hey, I had a really fun time last night.
噢是吗 对啊 我也是
Oh yeah? Yeah, yeah, Me too!
嗯 那啥 我觉得咱俩一块合作得不错 你跟我
Yeah, you know, I thought we made a good team, you and me.
嗯哼
Uh huh?
我们应该下次再试试看
We should do it again soon!
或者 嗯
Or, you know,
不一定要是游戏之夜啦 也不一定要跟别人一起之类的
it doesn't have to be a game night necessarily, with other people, or anything.
别的... 什么的 都行
It could be... whatever or...
啊 对 右边
Yeah, right. RIGHT!
嗯对...
Righhhhht...
反正你到时候找我吧
Well, just let me know.
基本上怎么都行 不好意思
I'm pretty much up for anything. Sorry!
喂
HEY!
老兄 你要干嘛
Dude! What are you doing?!
- 有个虫子  - 啥
- There was a bug! - What?!
我来处理
I got it!
瑞格比 你从哪..
Rigby! Where did you-
噢不 我的手机
Oh no! My phone!
等会 你手机
Wait, YOUR phone?!
是啊 艾琳去厕所了 让我帮她看着点电话
Yeah, Eileen told me to watch for calls while she was in the bathroom.
噢 给你
Oh, here.
天呢 谢了
Gee, thanks...
等等 那什么 那我能借你的电话用用吗
Wait, so, can I borrow YOUR phone then?
我忘了我把它放在哪了 可能在车里吧 还是哪来着
Oh, I don't know where I left it. Maybe in my car, or something?
你要想要的话我去帮你看看
I can go check if you want.
不用 没事 我们自己来
Oh, no no! We can get it.
你这还上着班呢 多不方便
You're still working and all, so...
就是 把钥匙给我们吧
Yeah, give us the keys!
好嘞 也行
Okay, that's cool.
我这趟班快上完了 到时候外边见
I'm almost done with my shift, so I'll just meet you out there.
没问题
Cool!
肯定在这里没跑啊
It's gotta be in here somewhere!
哥们 你就再打一次她手机呗
Dude, just butt dial her phone again,
一听铃声我们就知道手机在哪了
and then we can hear where it's ringing from!
你闭... 哎 其实这主意不错
Dude, shut... Actually, that's a good idea!
打通了 你听见铃声了没
It's ringing. Do you hear it?
- 喂 - 帕布
- Hello? - POPS?!
摩迪凯 你好呀
Mordecai, hello!
我正准备吃冰棒呢
I was just eating this frozen ice lolly,
然后突然 这个神奇的电话响起来了
when all of the sudden, this magical telephone thing started ringing!
玛格丽特肯定是昨天把她的手机落在咱们屋里了
Margaret must have left her phone at the house last night!
问问他吃的冰棒啥口味的
Ask him what flavor he is eating!
帕布 呆在那别动 知道吗
Pops, stay where you are, don't move, got it?
喔喔 我喜欢这个游戏
Oooh, I love this game!
好 咱们必须赶紧回去 趁着-
Okay, we need to get back to the house before-
嘿二位 找到我手机了吗
Hey guys! Did you find my phone?
找到了 落在我们家了
Yeah, back at the house!
好 我去拿回来
Great! I'll go pick it up!
不用 我们去给你拿
No! We can get it for you!
我是说 公园路途遥远
I mean, the park is so far out of your way!
没关系啦
I don't mind.
再说了 是我把手机落在那儿的
Besides, I'm the one that left it there!
好吧 咱们在那儿见
Fine. We'll see you there!
好 在那儿...
Okay, I'll see you...
见
there?
哥们 慢点
Dude! Slow down!
不行 不能让她听那条信息
No, she can't hear that message!
那就抄近道
Then take the shortcut!
谢了帕布
Thanks Pops!
一条新语音消息
One new voice message.
请输入密码
Please input password.
密码
PASSWORD?!
试试"咖啡"
Coffee!
密码错误 还有一次机会
Incorrect. You have one more attempt.
哥们 快点啊
Dude, hurry!
能是什么啊
What could it be?!
音乐 她喜欢"握拳"乐队
Music! She likes Fist Pump!
密码错误 您已没有机会
Incorrect. You have no more attempts.
再次尝试将被处罚
Any further attempts will be penalized.
哥们 她快到了 试试别的
Dude! She's almost here! Type something!
尝试太多次 你们将被惩罚
Too many attempts. You will now be penalized.
等等 啥玩意
Wait, what?
我赢了吗
Did I win?
起来
Get up.
搞什么
What the?
我们这是在哪
Where are we?
你们已在虚拟信息控制中心着陆
You have landed in the Virtual Messaging Control Center.
我们是语音信息的守护者们
We are the keepers of the voice mail.
守护着有史以来的所有信息
Guardians of all messages throughout history.
由于你们过多次的尝试
Because of your excessive attempts,
违背了密码法
you have violated password law,
你们已被指控试图黑入他人账户
and you are charged for trying to hack into someone's account.
啥 我以为警告是开玩笑的
What?! I didn't think that warning was real!
噢 当然是真的
Oh, it's very real!
烧死他们 烧死他们
Burn them! Burn them!
安静点 我们不准备烧死他们
Settle down, we're not going to burn them.
我们什么时候烧过人呀
When have we ever burned anybody?
我们要消除他们... 的存在
We will erase them... from existence.
消除
玛格丽特 你好啊
Oh, Margaret, hello!
嘿帕布 我来拿我的手机
Hey Pops! I came to pick up my phone.
原来那个把摩迪凯和瑞格比吸进去的手机是你的
Oh, so it was YOUR phone that Mordecai and Rigby were sucked into?
是啊...
Sure....
那你看见我手机了吗
so, have you seen my phone?
看到了看到了 请进请进
Yes, yes, come in, come in!
等等 等等
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
我们可以解释
We can explain!
说来听听
Proceed with your message.
我不小心录了条信息发到这个女孩 玛格丽特的手机上了
Okay, so I accidentally recorded this message on a girl, Margaret's phone.
没错 我们就是想在她听到之前删掉
Yeah, and we were just trying to delete it before she heard it!
但是你们为什么不能让她听见呢
But why not let this person hear the message?
因为他会羞愧死的
Because HE'LL die of embarrassment!
羞愧
Embarrassment?
是啊 听着
Yeah, look.
玛格丽特跟我现在的关系很复杂 行不
Margaret and I have a really complicated relationship, okay?
关系
Relationship?
没时间跟你说这些了
We don't have time for this!
拜托让我们把那条信息删了好吗
Can you please delete the message?
- 在这儿呢  - 谢了 帕布
- It's over there! - Thanks, Pops!
嘿 我有条短信
Oh, hey. I have a message!
有人在操作语音信息系统
Someone is accessing the voice mail system.
不要啊
Oh no.
拜托 求你了 让我删了那条消息吧
Please, I'm begging you, please delete that message!
输入密码
Input Password.
真没想到
Saw that one coming.
电话使用者
Phone user!
呃 喂 你是谁
Uh, yes? Hello? Who is this?
我们截下了两个想要不经过你允许
We intercepted two frauds attempting to
而操作你语音信箱的骗子
access your voicemail without your permission.
有一个号称跟你有复杂的关系
The one who claims to have a complicated relationship with you.
别听他们胡说 玛格丽特
Don't listen to them, Margaret!
没错 这些家伙疯了
Yeah, these guys are crazy!
摩迪凯 瑞格比
Mordecai? Rigby?
等等 你们想黑我的手机
Wait, you tried to hack into my phone?!
这是个意外
It was an accident!
我们不知道那是你的手机
We didn't know it was YOUR phone!
是啊 是噢
Yeah, right!
呃好吧 我们知道是你的手机 但是...
Well, we did know, but...
但是什么 我真不敢相信你们会做出这种事来
But what? I can't believe you would do something like that!
我真是看错人了
I TOTALLY misjudged you!
兄弟 你就赶紧说实话吧
Dude, just come clean already.
好吧 听着
Okay, look.
我坐在了我的手机上 一不小心...
So I sat on my phone, and accidentally-
他拿屁股误拨了你的电话
He called you with his butt!
没错
Yeah.
所以我不小心给你留了语音信息 那是我在唱首很二的歌
So I accidentally left you a voicemail with me singing this dumb song.
实在太尴尬了
It is really embarrassing.
所以我们想在你听到之前删掉它
So we tried to erase it before you heard it.
你什么 我要听那条留言
You what? I want to hear the message!
等下 玛格丽特 别
Wait, Margaret! Please!
不 我就要听
No, I want to hear it.
播放那条消息
Play the message!
新消息
New message.
♪跟玛格丽特一起玩 感觉真不错♪
♪A-hanging with Margaret just-a feels so good.♪
♪像我早就预知过♪
♪like I knew it would.♪
♪一起欢笑 一起享乐♪
♪Laughing together and-a having a blast.♪
- ♪希望这一直持续着♪ - 噢 天哪
♪And I hope it lasts forever.♪  - Oh, Geez!
♪不敢相信 她是那么火辣♪
♪I can't believe how hot she is.♪
♪让我内心 纠结如麻♪
♪Makes my insides feel like knotted twists.♪
♪她漂亮的脸蛋和长长的腿♪
♪Her pretty face and those long, long legs,♪
♪希望我们有一天 不只是朋友♪
♪and I hope someday we are more than just friends!♪
比我想象的还糟糕
It's worse than I thought!
闭嘴
Shut up!
♪是否还记得昨晚 我们双手的触碰♪
♪Do you remember last night when our hands touched?♪
♪我们抢夺骰子 你在笑着 如此种种♪
♪We were grabbing for the dice and you were laughing and such...♪
不错嘛
Not bad!
♪...给我一次机会
...then take a chance on me.♪
良曲
♪也许你就会看到我们在一起是多么完美♪
♪And maybe then you'll see how perfect we can be.♪
♪你和我 在一起 永远永远在一起♪
♪Together you and me for all eternity!♪
拜托 弄死我得了
Please just erase me.
♪好吧 没准那会在很久以后♪
♪Okay. Maybe that's a long, long time.♪
♪但人人都可以做梦♪
♪But a guy can dream, can't I?♪
停下吧 我听够了
Okay, stop! I heard enough!
纠结如麻
Like knotted twists?!
唱得真不错
That's TOO good!
至少她没讨厌你啊
At least she doesn't hate you!
你希望我们现在解决这两个黑客吗
Would you like us to erase these hackers now?
不用啦 我觉得他们吸取教训了
Nah. I think they learned their lesson!
很好 你们可以走了
Very well. You're free to go.
但是如果你愿意的话可以留下
But you could stay if you'd like.
我们组个乐队应该不错
We're thinking of forming a band!
出口
呃是吗 到时候电话联系
Oh, yeah, we'll give you a call.
好嘞 留个言就行 我们就能收到
Cool, just leave a message, and we'll get it.
等等 还没给他们我的号码呢
Oh wait. I didn't give them my number...
万岁 表现不错
Hooray! Good show!
嘿 嘿 我们回来了 谢啦 玛格丽特
Hey. HEY! We made it! Thanks, Margaret!
不客气
No problem!
是啊 谢了玛格丽特
Yeah, thanks Margaret!
没事儿
Sure thing!
嘿帕布 去别的房间 我给你看点东西
Hey, Pops. I need to show you something in the other room.
我喜欢看东西
I love being shown things!
那...
So...
那什么
So.
那啥 你要想的话现在就把消息删了吧
So, you could go ahead and erase the message now.
才不呢 那歌要删了也太可惜了
Oh, no! That song is WAY to good to lose!
啥 真的假的
What? Come on!
真的 我要把它设置成你的专属铃声
No actually, I'm going to set it to be your personal ringtone.
你在开玩笑吧
You're kidding, right?
没 这样每次你给我打电话我都能听你唱歌了
Nope. That way I can hear you singing every time you call me.
所以 最好给我打电话
So you better call me!
好呀
Okay!
下次我会用我手指拨电话的
I'll try to use my fingers to dail next time,
而不是屁股
and not my butt!
太赞了
Rad.